Planned Parenthood Federation of America Records (PPFA II): SERIES V. Affiliates, 1930-80 (Part 2)
Sophia Smith Collection
Planned Parenthood Federation of America Records (PPFA II): SERIES V. Affiliates (Part 2)
1921, 1939-1981
Planned Parenthood Federation of America
371a_s5_p2
65 linear feet
Sophia Smith Collection Smith College Northampton, MA
This series contains the national office's records on affiliate activities and includes minutes, affiliation materials, copies of correspondence, clippings, publicity, reports, and financial material.This Series forms part of the PPFA II Records
This Series forms part of the PPFA II Records
This series contains the national office's records on affiliate activities and includes minutes, affiliation materials, copies of correspondence, clippings, publicity, reports, and financial material.
The bulk of the material is arranged alphabetically by state. The first set of state material is local affiliates' minutes. This is followed by minutes and meeting material from regional offices; it is unclear whether this duplicates material contained in SERIES VI. REGIONS. Next comes general administrative material, which includes files on services offered by affiliates, including birth control methods and sexually transmitted disease education. The remainder of material, the bulk of this series, is from affiliate offices and filed by state. General state programs such as anti-poverty and migrant worker programs are filed first within a state, and then local and metropolitan affiliates are listed. Files include affiliate reports, statistics, publicity, and correspondence. There are some inconsistencies: New York City comes before New York State, but there is also New York City material within New York State and some at the end of the series. The state of Connecticut is filed last. It contains a significant amount of information regarding Griswold vs. Connecticut and the fight to disseminate birth control and contraceptive information. The New York State files contain some material pertaining to the relaxation of abortion laws in the early 1970s. The end of the series includes miscellany and histories of the regions.
NOTE: To view the series descriptions and contents lists, click on the series links below. Some files are quite large and may take several minutes to load, depending on your internet connection.
Due to it's large size, the SERIES V container list is divided into two parts: Part 1 and Part 2.
This collection is organized into ten series:
I. Chronological Files
II. Classified Files
Part 1
Part 2
III. Publications
IV. Subject Files
V. Affiliates
Part 1
Part 2
VI. Regions
VII. Minutes
VIII. Foreign
IX. Guttmacher
[X. Restricted]
PPFA has closed records created January 1, 1985 or later, with the exception of many published materials which are open to research. All records having to do with clinic defense and security are closed. PPFA has closed a small section of files in box 206 for fifty years. Researchers may request access to restricted materials from PPFA.
The Margaret Sanger Papers Microfilm Edition: Smith College Collection Series, edited by Esther Katz, et al., University Publications of America, 1995
Periodic additions to the collection are expected.
PPFA deposited these records in 1988. Various departments have since sent miscellaneous additions.
Best, Winfield; Guttmacher, Alan Frank, 1898-; McCormick, Katherine Dexter, 1876-1967; Rose, D. Kenneth; Sanger, Margaret, 1879-1966; Wattleton, Faye; Alan Guttmacher Institute--History; American Birth Control League--History; Abortion--Law and legislation-United States--History--Sources; Abortion services--History--Sources; Birth Control Clinical Research Bureau (New York, N.Y.)--History; Birth Control Federation of America--History; International Planned Parenthood Federation--History; Planned Parenthood Federation of America--History; Planned Parenthood-World Population (U.S.)--History; Birth control clinics--United States--History--Sources; Birth control--History--20th century--Sources; Birth control--Developing countries--History--20th century--Sources; Contraceptives--Research--History; Hygiene, Sexual--History--20th century; Human reproduction--Political aspects; Population policy--History--20th century; Reproductive health--Statistics; Sex instruction--History; Women--Health and hygiene--United States--20th century; Women's health services--United States--20th century
This Series forms part of the PPFA II Records
See also the PPFA I Records.
Related material can be found in the Margaret Sanger Papers, Sophia Smith Collection, Smith College, and at the Library of Congess.
- SERIES V. AFFILIATES (PART 2)
  - Montana
    - Anti-Poverty, 1967-1971 (Box 161, Folder 41)
    - Contacts, 1964-1974 (Box 161, Folder 42)
    - Estimated Status of Family Needs and Services in Montana, 1970-1971 (Box 161, Folder 43)
    - Legal, 1971 (Box 161, Folder 44)
    - Public Health from 1963
      - 1963-1972 (Box 161, Folder 45)
      - 1975-1978 (Box 161)
    - Public Welfare, 1960-1970 (Box 161, Folder 46)
    - Schools, General, 1966-1971 (Box 161, Folder 47)
    - State Pharmaceutical Association, 1971 (Box 161, Folder 48)
    - Billings
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws, 1963-1968 (Box 161, Folder 49)
      - Affiliation, PP Correspondence from 1963
        - 1963-1974 (Box 161, Folder 50)
        - 1975-1979 (Box 161)
      - PP Committee from 1964
        - 1964-1974 (Box 161, Folder 51)
        - 1975-1978 (Box 161)
      - Reports, General, 1965-1970 (Box 161, Folder 52)
      - Planned Parenthood, Reports, Members, 1964-1971 (Box 161, Folder 53)
      - Planned Parenthood, Publicity, 1963-1964 (Box 161, Folder 54)
      - Field Trips, 1961-1963 (Box 161, Folder 55)
    - Missoula
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws from 1967
        - 1967-1973 (Box 161, Folder 56)
        - 1976-1980 (Box 161)
      - Affiliation, PP Correspondence from 1967
        - 1967-1974 (Box 161, Folder 57)
        - 1975-1980 (Box 161)
      - PP from 1967
        - 1967-1974 (Box 161, Folder 58)
        - 1975-1978 (Box 161)
      - Reports, Members from 1967
        - 1967-1972 (Box 161, Folder 59)
        - 1975 (Box 161)
    - Bozeman, Midwest Region, Consultation Visits, Director Ralph D. Price, 1971 (Box 161, Folder 60)
    - Helena, Midwest Region, Consultation Visits, Director Ralph D. L. Price, 1971 (Box 161, Folder 61)
    - Midwest Region, Reports, Field Trips, 1971 (Box 161, Folder 62)
    - Western Region, Reports, Field Trips, 1965-1968 (Box 161, Folder 63)
    - General, Field Trips, 1961-1962 (Box 161, Folder 64)
  - Nebraska
    - Anti-Poverty, 1967-1974 (Box 161, Folder 65)
    - Contacts, 1965-1974 (Box 161, Folder 66)
    - Clergy, Counseling Services, 1972 (Box 161, Folder 67)
    - Hospitals, 1973 (Box 161, Folder 68)
    - Legal, 1957-1973 (Box 161, Folder 69)
    - Migrants, 1969 (Box 161, Folder 70)
    - Projects & Proposals, 1971 (Box 161, Folder 71)
    - Public Health, 1956-1968 (Box 161, Folder 72)
    - Public Welfare, 1967-1971 (Box 161, Folder 73)
    - Schools, General, 1964-1973 (Box 161, Folder 74)
    - Lincoln
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws from 1974
        - 1974 (Box 161, Folder 75)
        - 1975-1980 (Box 161)
      - Affiliation, PP of Lincoln, Correspondence from 1974
        - 1974 (Box 161, Folder 76)
        - 1975-1980 (Box 161)
      - PP of Lincoln, Trip Report, Andy Diaz, 1978 (Box 161, Folder 77)
      - PP of Lincoln from 1973
        - 1973-1974 (Box 161, Folder 78)
        - 1975-1980 (Box 161)
      - PP of Lincoln, Reports, Members, 1975-1976 (Box 161, Folder 79)
    - Omaha
      - Field Trips, 1955-1964 (Box 161, Folder 80)
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws from 1948
        - 1948-1973 (Box 161, Folder 81)
        - 1975-1979 (Box 161)
      - Affiliation, Correspondence from 1959
        - 1959-1974 (Box 161, Folder 82)
        - 1975-1980 (Box 161)
      - PP of Omaha Council, Bluffs, 1978-1979 (Box 162, Folder 1)
      - PP of Omaha (formerly PP Committee of Nebraska) from 1971
        - 1971-1974 (Box 162, Folder 2)
        - 1975-1977 (Box 162)
      - PP, Committee, 1963-1970 (Box 162, Folder 3)
      - PP Committee of Nebraska, Reports, Clinics, 1973 (Box 162, Folder 4)
      - Reports, General, 1966-1968 (Box 162, Folder 5)
      - Reports, Members from 1964
        - 1964-1974 (Box 162, Folder 6)
        - 1975 (Box 162)
      - Publicity, 1964-1980 (Box 162, Folder 7)
      - Midwest Region, Reports, Field Trips, 1966-1967 (Box 162, Folder 8)
  - Nevada
    - Contacts, 1968-1971 (Box 162, Folder 9)
    - Legal, 1973 (Box 162, Folder 10)
    - Field Trips, Reno, 1964-1970 (Box 162, Folder 11)
    - Public Health, 1964-1973 (Box 162, Folder 12)
    - Public Welfare, 1966-1970 (Box 162, Folder 13)
    - Las Vegas
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws from 1972
        - 1972 (Box 162, Folder 14)
        - 1974-1978 (Box 162)
      - Affiliation, PP Correspondence from 1972
        - 1972-1974 (Box 162, Folder 15)
        - 1975-1978 (Box 162)
      - PP of Southern Nevada, Inc., Legal (Paul, Eve), 1979 (Box 162, Folder 16)
      - PP of Southern Nevada from 1972
        - 1972-1974 (Box 162, Folder 17)
        - 1975 (Box 162)
      - PP of Southern Nevada, 1976-1978 (Box 162, Folder 18)
      - PP Southern Nevada, Inc., Reports, Members
        - 1972 (Box 162, Folder 19)
        - 1975-1978 (Box 162)
    - Reno
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws from 1972
        - 1972-1974 (Box 162, Folder 20)
        - 1975-1980 (Box 162)
      - Affiliation, PP Correspondence from 1972
        - 1972-1974 (Box 162, Folder 21)
        - 1975-1979 (Box 162)
      - PP of Northern Nevada, Legal (Paul, Eve), 1978 (Box 162, Folder 22)
      - PP of Northern Nevada, 1976-1980 (Box 162, Folder 23)
      - PP of Washoe County, Inc. from 1971
        - 1971-1974 (Box 162, Folder 24)
        - 1975 (Box 162)
      - PP of Washoe County, Reports, Members
        - 1971-1974 (Box 162, Folder 25)
        - 1976-1977 (Box 162)
    - Western Region, Reports, Field Trips, 1971-1972 (Box 162, Folder 26)
  - New Hampshire
    - Contacts from 1965
      - 1965-1970 (Box 162, Folder 27)
      - 1977-1980 (Box 162)
    - Public Health, 1962-1970 (Box 162, Folder 28)
    - Schools, General, 1963-1969 (Box 162, Folder 29)
    - Conway, PP Association of Carroll County, 1970-1973 (Box 162, Folder 30)
    - Keene
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws, 1968 (Box 162, Folder 31)
      - Affiliation, Correspondence, 1967-1971 (Box 162, Folder 32)
      - PP Correspondence, 1966-1969 (Box 162, Folder 33)
      - Reports, Members, 1966-1970 (Box 162, Folder 34)
    - Lebanon
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws from 1967
        - 1967-1974 (Box 162, Folder 35)
        - 1977-1978 (Box 162)
      - Affiliation, PP Association Upper Valley, Correspondence from 1967
        - 1967-1974 (Box 162, Folder 36)
        - 1975-1979 (Box 162)
      - PP Association Upper Valley, Trip Report, Andy Diaz, 1977-1978 (Box 162, Folder 37)
      - PP Association of the Upper Valley from 1966
        - 1966-1974 (Box 162, Folder 38)
        - 1977-1979 (Box 162)
      - Reports, General, 1967 (Box 162, Folder 39)
      - Reports, Members, 1967-1972 (Box 162, Folder 40)
    - Manchester PP, 1967-1968 (Box 162, Folder 41)
  - New Jersey
    - General, Correspondence, 1969-1970 (Box 162, Folder 42)
    - Anti-Poverty, 1965-1970 (Box 162, Folder 43)
    - Confederation of New Jersey Affiliates, 1973 (Box 162, Folder 44)
    - Contacts
      - 1962-1974 (Box 162, Folder 45)
      - 1975-1976 (Box 162)
    - Family Planning, Advisory Committee for Medicaid, 1970 (Box 162, Folder 46)
    - Family Planning, Public Affairs Office & Family Planning Newsletter, 1977 (Box 162, Folder 47)
    - New Jersey Family Planning Program from 1971
      - 1971 (Box 162, Folder 48)
      - 1975 (Box 162)
    - Hospitals, 1962-1972 (Box 162, Folder 49)
    - Legal, General from 1926
      - 1924-1969 (Box 162, Folder 50)
      - 1976-1978 (Box 162)
    - Legal, Kinney Case, Correspondence, 1959-1963 (Box 162, Folder 51)
    - Legal, Kinney Case, Preliminary Documents, 1959 (Box 162, Folder 52)
    - Legal, Kinney Case, News Clips, 1959 (Box 162, Folder 53)
    - Migrant, 1956-1968 (Box 162, Folder 54)
    - Projects, 1969-1970 (Box 162, Folder 55)
    - Public Health from 1960
      - 1960-1974 (Box 162, Folder 56)
      - 1978-1979 (Box 162)
    - Public Welfare, 1963-1973 (Box 162, Folder 57)
    - 21-County Family Planning Program, Inc., 1971-1972 (Box 162, Folder 58)
    - Background Relating to the Formation of 21-County Family Planning, Inc., 1970-1971 (Box 162, Folder 59)
    - United Fund, 1968-1969 (Box 162, Folder 60)
    - Schools, General, 1962-1974 (Box 162, Folder 61)
    - Princeton University, Correspondence, General, 1962-1969 (Box 162, Folder 62)
    - Rutgers State University, Correspondence, General, 1963-1970 (Box 162, Folder 63)
    - Conference of PP New Jersey Affiliates from 1974
      - 1974 (Box 162, Folder 64)
      - 1975-1979 (Box 162)
    - Bridgeton, Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws, 1963-1968 (Box 162, Folder 65)
    - Affiliation, Conference of New Jersey PP Affiliates, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws, 1974 (Box 162, Folder 66)
    - Bridgeton Area PP League, 1963-1967 (Box 162, Folder 67)
    - Affiliation, Conference of New Jersey PP Affiliates, Correspondence, 1974 (Box 162, Folder 68)
    - Bridgeton Area, Field Trips, 1963 (Box 162, Folder 69)
    - Bridgetown
      - PP League, Reports, General, 1964-1966 (Box 162, Folder 70)
      - PP League, Reports, Members, 1963-1966 (Box 162, Folder 71)
    - Camden
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws from 1955
        - 1951-1974 (Box 162, Folder 72)
        - 1977-1980 (Box 162)
      - Affiliation, PP League, Correspondence from 1957
        - 1959-1974 (Box 162, Folder 73)
        - 1977-1980 (Box 162)
      - PP Greater Camden Area, Legal (Paul, Eve), 1978-1979 (Box 162, Folder 74)
      - PP League from 1963
        - 1964-1974 (Box 162, Folder 75)
        - 1976-1979 (Box 162)
      - Field Trips, 1955-1964 (Box 162, Folder 76)
      - Reports, Clinics from 1967 (empty) (Box 162, Folder 77)
      - PP League, Reports, General, 1962-1968 (Box 162, Folder 78)
      - PP League, Reports, Members from 1963
        - 1963-1974 (Box 162, Folder 79)
        - 1975-1977 (Box 162)
      - PP League, Publicity, 1956-1966 (Box 162, Folder 80)
    - Hackensack
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws from 1956
        - 1956-1973 (Box 162, Folder 81)
        - 1976-1980 (Box 162)
      - Affiliation, Correspondence from 1961
        - 1961-1974 (Box 162, Folder 82)
        - 1975-1981 (Box 162)
      - PP Bergen County from 1969
        - 1969-1974 (Box 162, Folder 83)
        - 1975-1979 (Box 162)
      - PP Center Bergen County, 1962-1968 (Box 162, Folder 84)
      - PP Center, Reports, Clinics, 1960-1969 (Box 162, Folder 85)
      - PP Center, Reports, General, 1964-1965 (Box 163, Folder 1)
      - PP Center, Reports, Members from 1963
        - 1962-1972 (Box 163, Folder 2)
        - 1975-1976 (Box 163)
      - PP Center, Publicity, 1962-1965 (Box 163, Folder 3)
      - Field Visits, 1973 (Box 163, Folder 4)
      - Field Trip, 1956-1964 (Box 163, Folder 5)
    - Hoboken, Field Trips, 1964 (Box 163, Folder 6)
    - Jersey City
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws from 1963
        - 1963-1972 (Box 163, Folder 7)
        - 1975 (Box 163)
      - Affiliation, PP Hudson County, Correspondence from 9/63
        - 1963-1974 (Box 163, Folder 8)
        - 1975-1979 (Box 163)
      - PP Association of Hudson County from 1963
        - 1963-1974 (Box 163, Folder 9)
        - 1975-1979 (Box 163)
      - Reports, General, 1963 (Box 163, Folder 10)
      - Reports, Members, 1963-1968 (Box 163, Folder 11)
      - Field Visits from 1974
        - 1974 (Box 163, Folder 12)
        - 1975-1977 (Box 163)
      - Field Trips, 1963-1964 (Box 163, Folder 13)
    - Levittown, PP Committee, 1961 (Box 163, Folder 14)
    - Madison
      - PP, 1962-1970 (Box 163, Folder 15)
      - PP, Reports, General, 1961-1965 (Box 163, Folder 16)
      - PP, Reports, Members, 1961-1967 (Box 163, Folder 17)
      - Field Trips, 1962 (Box 163, Folder 18)
    - Morristown
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws from 1951
        - 1951-1974 (Box 163, Folder 19)
        - 1977-1980 (Box 163)
      - Affiliation, PP Correspondence, 1961-1973 (Box 163, Folder 20)
      - PP of Northwest New Jersey, Legal (Paul, Eve), 1979 (Box 163, Folder 21)
      - PP of Northwest New Jersey, Trip Report, Andy Diaz, 1977 (Box 163, Folder 22)
      - PP Center from 1963
        - 1963-1974 (Box 163, Folder 23)
        - 1974-1980 (Box 163)
      - Field Trips, 1960-1964 (Box 163, Folder 24)
      - Reports, Clinics, 1973 (Box 163, Folder 25)
      - Reports, General from 1960
        - 1960-1967 (Box 163, Folder 26)
        - 1975-1979 (Box 163)
      - Reports, Members, 1961-1972 (Box 163, Folder 27)
      - Publicity, 1964-1978 (Box 163, Folder 28)
    - Newark
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws from 1956
        - 1956-1972 (Box 163, Folder 29)
        - 1975 (Box 163)
      - Affiliation, PP Correspondence from 1959
        - 1959-1974 (Box 163, Folder 30)
        - 1975-1978 (Box 163)
      - Field Trips, 1954-1963 (Box 163, Folder 31)
      - Essex County Committee for PP from 1970
        - 1970-1974 (Box 163, Folder 32)
        - 1975-1981 (Box 163)
      - PP Committee Essex County, 1964-1969 (Box 163, Folder 33)
      - PP Committee, Reports, Clinics, 1960-1965 (Box 163, Folder 34)
      - PP Committee, Reports, General, 1963-1970 (Box 163, Folder 35)
      - PP Committee, Reports, Members, 1963-1970 (Box 163, Folder 36)
      - PP Committee, Publicity, 1964-1969? (Box 163, Folder 37)
    - New Brunswick
      - Affiliation, PP Middlesex County (formerly Edison), Audits, Budgets, Bylaws from 1972
        - 1972-1974 (Box 163, Folder 38)
        - 1977-1980 (Box 163)
      - Affiliation, PP Middlesex County (formerly Edison) from 1972
        - 1972-1974 (Box 163, Folder 39)
        - 1975-1979 (Box 163)
      - PP Middlesex County (formerly Edison) from 1972
        - 1972-1974 (Box 163, Folder 40)
        - 1976-1981 (Box 163)
      - Field Visits, 1973-1974 (Box 163, Folder 41)
      - PP League of Middlesex County, Reports, Members, 1974 (Box 163, Folder 42)
    - Paterson
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws from 1949
        - 1949-1974 (Box 163, Folder 43)
        - 1975-1980 (Box 163)
      - Affiliation, Correspondence from 1960
        - 1960-1974 (Box 163, Folder 44)
        - 1975-1979 (Box 163)
      - Passaic County PP Center, Trip Report, Andy Diaz, 1977 (Box 163, Folder 45)
      - PP Passaic County from 1962
        - 1962-1974 (Box 163, Folder 46)
        - 1975-1979 (Box 163)
      - Reports, General, 1968 (Box 163, Folder 47)
      - Reports, Members, 1964-1970 (Box 163, Folder 48)
      - Publicity, 1962 (Box 163, Folder 49)
      - Field Visits from 1974
        - 1974 (Box 163, Folder 50)
        - 1976-1978 (Box 163)
    - Plainfield
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws from 1949
        - 1949-1974 (Box 163, Folder 51)
        - 1977-1979 (Box 163)
      - Affiliation, PP of Union County Area, Inc., (formerly Tri-County League), Correspondence from 1961
        - 1961-1974 (Box 163, Folder 52)
        - 1976-1981 (Box 163)
      - PP of Union County Area, Inc. (formerly Tri-County League) from 1964
        - 1964-1974 (Box 163, Folder 53)
        - 1975-1979 (Box 163)
      - Merger: Plainfield, Westfield, Tri-County PP, 1963-1965 (Box 163, Folder 54)
      - PP of Union County, Legal (Paul, Eve), 1978 (Box 163, Folder 55)
      - PP Tri-County League, Chapters, Reports, Clinics, 1972 (Box 163, Folder 56)
      - PP Tri-County League, Reports, Clinics, 1971 (Box 163, Folder 57)
      - Reports, General, 1962-1964 (Box 163, Folder 58)
      - Reports, Members, 1961-1973 (Box 163, Folder 59)
      - Field Trips, 1961 (Box 163, Folder 60)
    - Princeton
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws, 1951-1961 (Box 163, Folder 61)
      - PP Committee, 1962-1969 (Box 163, Folder 62)
      - Reports, Members, 1959-1970 (Box 163, Folder 63)
      - Field Trips, 1948-1962 (Box 163, Folder 64)
    - Shrewsbury
      - Affiliation, PP Monmouth County (formerly Red Bank), Audits, Budgets, Bylaws from 1957
        - 1959-1972 (Box 163, Folder 65)
        - 1975-1978 (Box 163)
      - Affiliation, PP of Monmouth County, Inc. (formerly Red Bank - Asbury Park), Correspondence from 1961
        - 1961-1972 (Box 163, Folder 66)
        - 1975-1980 (Box 163)
      - PP of Monmouth County, Field Visits, 1977 (Box 163, Folder 67)
      - PP Monmouth County (formerly Red Bank), Field Visits, 1974 (Box 163, Folder 68)
    - Asbury Park, PP of Monmouth County, Field Trips, 1957-1964 (Box 163, Folder 69)
    - Shrewsbury
      - PP of Monmouth County (formerly in Red Bank) from 1972
        - 1972-1974 (Box 163, Folder 70)
        - 1975-1979 (Box 163)
      - PP of Monmouth County (formerly in Red Bank & Asbury Park), 1962-1971 (Box 163, Folder 71)
      - PP of Monmouth County (formerly in Red Bank & Asbury Park), Publicity, 1956-1974 (Box 163, Folder 72)
      - PP of Monmouth County (formerly in Red Bank & Asbury Park), Reports, General, 1963-1971 (Box 163, Folder 73)
      - PP of Monmouth County, Reports, Members, 1963-1974 (Box 163, Folder 74)
    - Trenton
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws from 1961
        - 1961-1973 (Box 163, Folder 75)
        - 1976-1979 (Box 163)
      - Affiliation, PP Correspondence from 1961
        - 1961-1973 (Box 163, Folder 76)
        - 1976-1981 (Box 163)
      - PP Association of Mercer Area from 1969
        - 1969-1974 (Box 163, Folder 77)
        - 1975-1978 (Box 163)
      - PP Association Mercer Area, 1963-1968 (Box 163, Folder 78)
      - PP Mercer Area, Reports, Clinics, 1964-1968 (Box 164, Folder 1)
      - PP Mercer Area, Reports, Members, 1962-1974 (Box 164, Folder 2)
      - PP Mercer Area, Reports, General, 1963-1972 (Box 164, Folder 3)
      - PP Mercer Area, Publicity, 1963-1970 (Box 164, Folder 4)
      - Field Trips, 1959-1964 (Box 164, Folder 5)
    - Westfield
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws, 1950-1965 (Box 164, Folder 6)
      - Affiliation, PP Correspondence, 1959-1968 (Box 164, Folder 7)
      - PP Committee, 1961-1969 (Box 164, Folder 8)
      - Reports, Members, 1961-1963 (Box 164, Folder 9)
      - Publicity, 1961-1962 (Box 164, Folder 10)
      - Field Trips, 1959-1961 (Box 164, Folder 11)
    - General, Field Trips, 1955-1965 (Box 164, Folder 12)
    - Migrant, Field Trips, 1958-1962 (Box 164, Folder 13)
    - Mid-Atlantic Region, Reports, Field Trips, 1965-1974 (Box 164, Folder 14)
  - New York City
    - Anti-Poverty, 1965-1969 (Box 164, Folder 15)
    - Contacts, 1962-1967 (Box 164, Folder 16)
    - Forte Green: Neighborhood Profile for Block Communities, Inc., 1968 (Box 164, Folder 17)
    - NYC Health & Hospitals Corporation, Hyde Amendment Injunction Department Hew, 1976 (Box 164, Folder 18)
    - Hospitals, General, Correspondence from 1966
      - 1966-1970 (Box 164, Folder 19)
      - 1975 (Box 164)
    - Hospitals, General, Correspondence, 1964-1965 (Box 164, Folder 20)
    - Hospitals, Reports & General, 1944-1965 (Box 164, Folder 21)
  - Anatomy of a Victory, 1959 (Box 164, Folder 22)
  - Anatomy of a Victory, Support Letters, 1958 (Box 164, Folder 23)
  - Anatomy of a Victory, Memo Material, 1958 (Box 164, Folder 24)
  - Anatomy of a Victory, Workfile, 1957-1958 (Box 164, Folder 25)
  - Anatomy of a Victory, II, 1961 (Box 164, Folder 26)
  - New York City
    - Hospitals, Field Trips, 1964 (Box 164, Folder 27)
    - New York Inter-Agency Council on Family Planning, 1971 (Box 164, Folder 28)